## Jesse Sargent

### **EDUCATION**

Year 12 Certificate

### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Academic achievement Awards
With all They Might Award
Certificate of Graduation – Kelvin Grove State College
RSA –Responsible Service of Alcohol
Statement of Attainment – Work safely in the Construction Industry

### **CONTACT DETAILS**

27 Frost st, Mount Gravatt 4122 QLD

Mobile: 0404 311 732 Email: jesse.sarg@gmail.com

## **SUMMARY**

I have completed my High School Certificate and endeavour to go to university to study a bachelor of science in 2014.

I understand the work ethic and have the ability to focus on my work. I enjoy working and keeping myself productive.

I am a quiet but happy and giving person. Growing up I was the youngest to three older brothers who have developed good coping skills in me.

My interests are Music. I play guitar, sing and previously strived to improve my schools band for around 3 years. The beach is also a big part of my life where I enjoy staying active and keeping fit.

## **AVALIABILITY**

I have just moved in to Mount Gravatt and am currently looking for any work around the area. As of now i have no other prior commitments and plan to make work a priority. I am more then happy to work weekdays and or weekends wether they be day or night shifts.

## **REFEREES**

Florian Steinbacher (Griffith University) - 0407 698 168

Daniel Watson (Grifith University) - 0411 801 179

Larrisa Moore (The Daily Grind Coffee Bar) - 0433 925 393

### WORK EXPERIENCE

### DOMINOS (Spring Hill, Brisbane) November 2008 – March 2009

- Creating and preparing pizzas and ingredients
- Customer service
- Cutting and packaging pizzas
- Washing dishes and cleaning
- Cash handling skills

I had a good relationship with all my work collegues and enjoyed working in a fast food environment, mainly because of the challenge. Everything is fast pace and I enjoyed always being on the ball. I also found that working for a fast food chain taught me quite a lot about cleaning and preparing the work station thoroughly as well as the handling and calculating of money.

## PEPE'S MEXICAN RESTAURANT (Newmarket, Brisbane) June 2011 - August 2011

- Customer service
- Table waiting
- Cash handling skills

As I was on my way to finishing school, my father was also finishing up his work in Brisbane and transferring to Toowoomba. I saw the best thing for me to do was to move down to live with my mother in Casuarina. Unfortunately due to this move I had to leave Pepe's. I thoroughly enjoyed the work place environment and tried my best at every opportunity.

## THE DAILY GRIND COFFEE BAR (Kingscliff, Twead Coast) January 2013 - December 2013

- Food preparation and table service.
- Cash handling skills
- Coffee making
- Cleaning duties

Throughout 2013 I worked casually at a small coffee bar. Altough only working there on weekends and days I had spare due to previous work I found it quite easy to pick up on the skills needed to preform my job to the best of my abilities. I also found myself learning new skills such as the art of coffee making and also better customer service.

# GRIFFITH UNIVERSITY GOLDCOAST CAMPUS (Southport, Goldcoast) February 2012 – March 2014

- Customer service
- Trade skills
- Cleaning
- Handyman work

The past 2 years working as a Trade Assistant for Griffith University has taught me much in the way of work ethic. Most of these 2 years were spent working 5 days weeks along side Tradesmen twice my age. My job entailed working with the Tradesmen employed by Griffith University but also doing small minor handyman works for the different people and departments around the campus. Although i throughly enjoyed the work environment I was in, I was finding it hard to get to work after I moved back to brisbane and therefore had to leave.